[wind howling]
[footsteps approaching]
[hinges creak]
[exhales]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[crow cawing]
[host] Tuesday has begun.
[ZZONE] This is driving me crazy.
ZZONE
It's so strange.
Shit.
ANOTHER HUNTER ON TUESDAY
SHIN JIEUN
[Jieun] I think I'm screwed right now.
[panting softly]
I need to tag someone.
[panting]
[ZZONE] Where did they go?
Where is everyone?
[ZZONE] I was so anxious and desperate
that I was panicking.
[panting, exhales]
You need to tag just anyone.
All I could think about
was not coming in last,
so I came to the conclusion
that the only way I'd survive
was by eliminating ZZONE.
So I went up to Joonsu
and just immediately said...
-Help.
-[Joonsu] What's wrong?
JIEUN GOES TO HER ALLY JOONSU
WHO WAS HIDING
I need your help with tagging others.
LEE JOONSU, SHIN JIEUN
[Joonsu] We don't have much time.
What's your score?
[Jieun] I'm at minus 18.
[Joonsu] Is there anyone else
with a lower score?
[Jieun] Can you give me two points?
LOOKING AROUND
-[Joonsu] Go ahead. Go ahead.
-If I end up...
JIEUN TAGS JOONSU
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Jieun] If I end up being eliminated,
-I won't pick you.
-[Joonsu] Okay.
SHIN JIEUN
-Let's do that.
-[Jieun] Sorry.
-[Joonsu] No worries.
-I had to beg you.
-[Joonsu] No, this is about being loyal.
-[Jieun] I'm sorry.
I wasn't at risk of getting eliminated.
It's better to help her now
so she can return the favor later
instead of refusing to help her.
That was my strategy.
MEANWHILE, ZZONE HASN'T FOUND ANYONE
[ZZONE] This is insane.
[sighs] This is driving me nuts.
-[alarm blaring]
-Gosh, that scared me.
[host] Wednesday has begun.
[ZZONE] I'm in trouble now.
I was a Wolf on Wednesday.
That day, there were five Wolves
and three Hunters.
There were way too many.
To avoid getting eliminated
without betraying anyone,
I figured the best thing to do
was hold out as long as possible.
So, I stayed hidden
even while I was a Wolf.
[♪ tense music playing]
I was trying to hold out anyway I could.
MUYEONG FACTORY
JANG EUNSIL
JANG EUNSIL HEADS TOWARD ZZONE
[ZZONE whispering]
The footsteps sound so loud.
I'm losing my mind.
[footsteps approaching]
[♪ sinister music playing]
-[Eunsil] I put it on.
-I put it on. I tagged you.
-[host] Tag confirmed.
-[Eunsil] It's okay. My arm...
-[ZZONE] I was so startled.
-Me too. [sighs]
ZZONE AND EUNSIL TAG EACH OTHER
[ZZONE groans] I was so frustrated.
If I held out a little longer,
it would have worked out.
I can't believe I got tagged there.
I was so mad at myself.
[host] Ms. ZZONE.
With a score of negative 23 points,
you've become an elimination candidate,
so please head to the Isolation Area.
[ZZONE] I guess Eunsil was a Hunter.
ZZONE HAS BEEN ISOLATED
FOR SCORING -20 POINTS OR LOWER
When I saw that message,
I was glad it wasn't me.
I felt a little relieved.
[sniffles]
[woodchips rustling]
I'm dizzy.
[sighs]
I decided to keep my head down
and not draw attention to myself.
I was going to lay low and wait it out.
JIEUN MUST HOLD OUT SOMEHOW
[Horseking] I'm a Hunter on Wednesday.
HORSEKING
[Horseking] In the second round,
I needed to stay in first place,
so I figured I had to widen the gap
between me and the other players.
Also, I suspected Sanghyun was the Seeker,
and I didn't want him to get
the Elimination Immunity Pass.
That was my goal.
YUK JUNSEO
[Junseo] I was a Wolf on Wednesday.
I did care about getting first place,
so I was very determined to catch people.
[Horseking exhales]
Where are they?
[groans] I need to tag people
while I'm a Hunter.
[sighs]
[Horseking] Geez.
Finding someone
would be a miracle at that point
because everyone was hiding,
so I couldn't see anyone.
They've all hidden so well.
As expected,
I knew everyone would be hiding.
But to me...
Jaegyun!
Hey, Jaegyun!
Jaegyun was there.
-Jaegyun!
-[Jaegyun] Yeah?
[Horseking] Help me.
I'll be in first if I tag someone.
[Jaegyun] Then, I'll be minus 10...
If you come in last place, I'll save you.
-Sure, go ahead.
-Thank you.
HORSEKING TAGS JAEGYUN
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Jaegyun] If I'm put up for elimination,
don't vote me out.
[Horseking] Of course not. Thank you.
I realized politics would matter more
from that point on.
People may not know this,
but I'm pretty good at politics.
I thought this could work
in my favor after all.
LAST NIGHT
MEN'S QUARTERS
[Horseking] If...
If you join our alliance, by any chance,
would we really need to fight each other?
No, never.
[Horseking] I mean, we don't want
to end up in last place.
HORSEKING JOINS FORCES WITH ROOMMATES
[Horseking] Joonsu!
JOONSU WAS PART OF TWO SEPARATE ALLIANCES
[footsteps]
I need to tag three people now
to be in first place.
But I'm at minus 7 points right now.
Last place has already been decided.
-Then, that's settled?
-Yeah.
-Tag me.
-Okay, thank you.
HORSEKING TAGS JOONSU
-Let's go. Get going.
-[host] Tag confirmed.
Thanks to Jaegyun and Joonsu,
things went the way I wanted,
and I could play with ease.
I got four points
just by convincing people.
On top of that...
There's someone over there.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[chuckles]
I even found Jieun, who was hiding.
-Sorry?
-[Horseking] What's your score?
[Jieun] Me? 10...
Earlier, I was tagged.
So, what's your score?
[Jieun] You're in first,
so why are you chasing?
-Why bother?
-You never know.
I promise I'm going to stay here,
but if you really have to...
If you have no choice later,
can't you come back then?
I'm begging you, I promise I'll stay here.
-[chuckles]
-I swear, I'll stay right here.
Seriously, I'll keep hiding.
Hold on.
-Here.
-No, wait.
HORSEKING TAGS JIEUN
To be honest, I did hesitate for a moment,
but I had to win.
I guess I only focused on my own survival.
[host] Tag confirmed.
[♪ ominous music plays]
JANG EUNSIL APPEARS
[Eunsil] What are you?
Oh.
[exclaims]
[exclaims] Wait a minute.
[Eunsil] I got you.
EUNSIL TAGS JUNSEO
[host] Tag confirmed.
Are you a Hunter?
Yeah, I'm a Hunter.
JANG EUNSIL
[Junseo] Eunsil charged at me
like a runaway train,
and I was totally stunned.
-I'd like to check my score, please.
-[dealer] Sure, we will check your score.
Your current score is two points.
YUK JUNSEO
[Junseo] Still,
my rank wasn't as low as I'd feared,
so I was very relieved.
At that point,
I put my Wolf and Hunter marker
on Wednesday and Friday respectively.
I thought maybe I should tag
as many people as I could on Friday.
Could you please check my placement?
PLAYERS CAN CHECK THEIR MARKER PLACEMENT
[dealer] You are a Wolf on Wednesday
and a Hunter on Tuesday.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
Okay.
What is going on?
I checked the placement chart again.
I saw that my Hunter marker
had been moved to Tuesday.
[dealer] Mr. Yuk Junseo,
please place your marker
on the game board.
You have placed
your Hunter marker on Friday.
Is this correct?
[Junseo] I put my Hunter marker on Friday.
For Wednesday and Friday,
I'd worked out my plan
to secure points on each day.
But when I saw the change,
my mind went blank for five seconds.
All my plans fell apart
because my chance as a Hunter disappeared.
I thought it might have
something to do with the Seeker's mission.
Ah, I'm in trouble.
HORSEKING
YOUN SANGHYUN
YUK JUNSEO
[Horseking] I'm exhausted. [sighs]
[exhales]
EUNSIL TAGGED JUNSEO
Yuk Junseo was caught.
I thought, "This is my game."
I wanted to win my own game.
IN FIRST WITH 11 POINTS
I absolutely didn't want
to lose to Sanghyun.
I had to win, no matter what.
LOCKED IN
[alarm blaring]
[Sanghyun] Gosh, it's so cramped.
ROUND 2 THURSDAY
What the heck?
-You... I'm a Hunter.
-What?
What are you?
-[host] Tag confirmed.
-I caught him.
SANGHYUN TAGS HORSEKING
Gosh, I almost lost it.
All I had to do was stay hidden,
and I had it in the bag.
[hisses frustratedly]
But then, by incredible coincidence,
Sanghyun came out
right next to me when he was a Wolf.
-You... I'm a Hunter.
-What?
[Horseking] Before I knew it,
he tagged me.
I was like, "What just happened?"
It felt a little off.
He didn't hesitate at all.
Whether it's this game or any other game,
if you tag the wrong person,
you lose points,
because the other person
could be a Hunter.
So naturally,
you need to keep your guard up.
There's no way you can win
if you play like he did.
I was like, "What was that?"
Did he already know?
-What?
-[Sanghyun] Wait, you're a Hunter?
[Horseking] Yeah.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
-[Sanghyun] Then, I'm screwed.
-[Horseking] That's right.
-What can you do?
-I wondered why you stayed still.
HORSEKING, YOUN SANGHYUN
[Sanghyun] Sure.
[patch rips]
-[dealer] Sanghyun has tagged Horseking.
-I'm so scared!
SANGHYUN RUNS AWAY AS SOON AS HE LEAVES
[Horseking] Is he really the Seeker?
[panting]
[dealer] Mr. Youn Sanghyun,
would you like to check your score?
-Would you like to check your score?
-[Sanghyun] No, thank you.
[♪ intriguing music intensifies]
Here.
TUESDAY, WEDNESDAY,
THURSDAY, FRIDAY, SATURDAY
ZZONE, JIEUN, JIMIN
JOONSU, JUNSEO,
EUNSIL, HORSEKING
SANGHYUN, JIMIN, EUNSIL
SANGHYUN CHECKS ALL THE MARKER PLACEMENTS
THURSDAY
SANGHYUN, JIMIN, EUNSIL
I knew.
I got it.
30 MINUTES AGO
ROUND 2 TUESDAY
[♪ mysterious music playing]
The dealer in the Placement Room
was wearing contact lenses.
I was like, "Why would he do that?"
[Junseo] Do wolves usually have
different-colored eyes?
[Jaegyun] It's heterochromia.
Different colored eyes.
[Jimin] Don't you think
there are too many Wolves?
[Jaegyun] But there are only nine of us.
[Sanghyun] He had a tag on him.
He had a tag that the players have.
So he's a Wolf.
Could I see your back for a moment?
[host] Tag confirmed.
[dealer] Mr. Youn Sanghyun.
You have obtained a Marker Movement Pass.
SANGHYUN, ZZONE, JIEUN
[gasps]
You may check
the marker placements of all players
and move one of your markers
to a different time slot.
ZZONE, JOONSU, SANGHYUN
Except for Wednesday,
to place your marker on a day
that already has three markers,
you must push one marker out
before placing yours.
Here is your marker
to show you have obtained
the Marker Movement Pass.
HIDDEN MARKER
THE PLAYER WHO TAGS THE HIDDEN WOLF CAN
VIEW MARKER PLACEMENTS OF ALL PLAYERS
MOVE ONE OF THEIR MARKERS ONCE
PUSH OUT A MARKER AND REASSIGN IT
IF CHOSEN DAY IS FULL
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[Sanghyun] First, I placed a Hunter marker
on Friday, which had only one other Hunter
and pushed out Junseo's Hunter marker.
Tuesday.
I moved Junseo's Hunter marker to Tuesday
and pushed out my Wolf marker.
Then, I pushed
Thursday's Hunter Joonsu out.
Horseking wasn't on Thursday,
so I was the only one who could hunt.
THURSDAY
EUNSIL, JIMIN, SANGHYUN
Given how strong Horseking is physically,
I saw him as a threat.
Since this game involves tagging people,
I thought I couldn't win
through a battle of wits alone.
PLACEMENT STATUS
TUE, WED
SANGHYUN
FRI: SANGHYUN
TUE: JUNSEO
THU: SANGHYUN
SAT: JOONSU
THU, FRI
SANGHYUN
-Thank you.
-[dealer] You're welcome.
SANGHYUN GOES LOOKING FOR A DOG
[Sanghyun] I have to catch ZZONE.
HWANG JAEGYUN
SANGHYUN GOES STRAIGHT TO JAEGYUN
-[Jaegyun chuckles] Seriously... Come on.
-[Sanghyun laughs]
SANGHYUN TAGS JAEGYUN
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Jaegyun] Something's off.
How did Sanghyun know that I was a Dog?
SANGHYUN TAGGED JAEGYUN
[Horseking] So this is how the game
has turned out.
I'm a Wolf.
-[alarm blaring]
-I can go in.
[host] Friday has begun.
[Horseking] To stay in first place,
I had to tag everyone I could
when I was a Wolf.
I thought I had to go for the win.
[Sanghyun] It was pretty much a fight
between me and Horseking.
I knew I had to take first place
so I wouldn't be voted as the Seeker.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
I need to catch them.
In Round 1, there were definitely
a lot of people around.
But when Round 2 started, it got quiet.
I didn't see anyone around.
ON THE OTHER HAND
[Horseking laughing]
-[Eunsil] Oh, my gosh!
-What are you?
1ST PLACE HORSEKING
8 POINTS
[host] Tag confirmed.
1ST PLACE HORSEKING
11 POINTS
2ND PLACE SANGHYUN
9 POINTS
Where are they?
HORSEKING'S LEAD ONCE AGAIN WIDENS
[panting]
[Sanghyun] I was looking everywhere,
but I couldn't find a single person.
But Horseking somehow kept finding people
and scoring points. I was amazed.
How was Horseking
tagging all those people?
[sighs]
It was hard to find people.
What are you?
[♪ tense music playing]
-[Junseo] What are you?
-Come on out first.
-What?
-[Junseo] What are you?
-I'm...
-A Wolf.
-[Junseo] If you're a Wolf, just go away.
-Why?
-[Junseo] There's no reason to fight.
-[Sanghyun] Why?
-Because I'm a Wolf.
-What?
-[Junseo] Because I'm a Wolf.
[exclaims]
[dealer] Yuk Junseo's Hunter marker.
Where would you like to move it?
Tuesday.
SANGHYUN KNOWS JUNSEO'S ROLE
-Junseo.
-[Junseo] You want to fight?
[panting]
SANGHYUN TAGS JUNSEO
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Junseo] How could you do that?
HORSEKING, SANGHYUN TIED
SANGHYUN COMES BACK WITH A TAG
[Sanghyun] Horseking's busy finding
-and catching people right now.
-[Junseo] I know.
ROUND 2 CURRENT RANKINGS
HORSEKING, SANGHYUN TIED FOR FIRST
[alarm blaring]
[host] Saturday has begun.
-[Sanghyun] I need to win anyway.
-Who are the Wolves?
Who are the other ones?
I don't know. I'm not sure about that.
How did you know I wasn't a Wolf then?
You just looked scared.
-What?
-You looked scared.
[Junseo] On what days were you a Hunter?
-[Sanghyun] I'll explain later.
-How?
[Sanghyun] I can't tell you right now.
[Junseo] Don't make
the explanation confusing.
If you confuse me,
I'll accuse you of being the Seeker.
Well, I can't tell you right now.
Why not? It's just us. Why can't you talk?
-The game's not over.
-Don't try to confuse me.
-The game isn't over yet.
-Huh?
[Sanghyun] Junseo suddenly went,
"You're the Seeker, right? Explain."
Then, he started to get angry at me.
The game is almost over now.
[Sanghyun exhales]
There's nothing I can do anyway.
[Sanghyun] But I couldn't tell him
anything either.
[sighs]
Horseking is way too fast.
YUK JUNSEO
[Junseo] Sanghyun's
been giving off this vibe
that makes him seem really suspicious.
I figured he had to be the Seeker.
If the Seeker ends up
claiming first place too,
it'll put everyone else at huge risk too.
[Sanghyun] Hold on! [laughing]
[Sanghyun panting]
SANGHYUN RUNS AWAY
TO THE PLACEMENT ROOM
Even Junseo,
the one person I thought I could trust,
began to suspect me.
I had no one to turn to.
RULE: CANNOT STAY IN PLACEMENT ROOM
FOR OVER TWO MINUTES
[panting]
[exhales]
What?
-[grunts]
-[host] Tag confirmed.
SANGHYUN AND JUNSEO TAG EACH OTHER
It was at the same time.
[both panting]
-We can't do this.
-[Junseo] What?
We can't do this.
[sighs]
I thought there was no way
I could let Horseking win
for being more athletic.
Even though he played football,
I decided I had to catch him.
I had to face him head-on.
-Horseking.
-Are you going to tag me?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-[grunts]
-[Sanghyun laughs]
HORSEKING BARELY GETS AWAY
He's gone.
HORSEKING'S INCREDIBLE ATHLETIC ABILITY
[Sanghyun] He's so good.
[exhales]
If he wins simply
because of his physical abilities...
[sighs frustratedly]
I decided to do everything I could.
[panting] Where... where are we now?
[Horseking] Even when I was
running out of breath, I gave it my all.
I didn't want to lose to Sanghyun.
He was the prime Seeker suspect,
so I can't let him get
the Elimination Immunity Pass.
[Sanghyun] Seriously, please. Please.
[alarm blaring]
[host] "Time Between Dogs and Wolves"
has ended.
[mic feedback]
Please gather in the Main Hall.
We will announce
the results of the Main Match.
[Horseking] If my math is right,
I should be in first place.
[Sanghyun] Please.
I wanted to come in first.
[host] In today's Main Match,
"Time Between Dogs and Wolves,"
the winner is...
Youn Sanghyun.
-[Jaegyun gasps in awe]
-[Joonsu] What?
-That's incredible.
-[Joonsu exclaims]
[players applauding]
Geez, I thought
I was in a tie for first place.
[hisses frustratedly]
Is this how things ended up?
[Sanghyun] I would've been
in serious danger
without the Marker Movement Pass.
If I were to say how much that pass
contributed to my win,
I'd say it was 100%.
WHEN HE USED THE HIDDEN PASS
I pushed out Junseo's marker.
[inaudible dialogue]
And then, with my Wolf marker
that was pushed out,
I pushed out Joonsu's Hunter marker
on Thursday
and put my Wolf marker on Thursday.
-[dealer] Where would you like to move it?
-To Saturday.
After being pushed out,
Joonsu's marker was left.
But I didn't want to waste it.
I thought about where I could place it
to give me an advantage.
[breathes deeply]
-That Hunter...
-[dealer] Yes?
[Sanghyun] Yeah, if I place
Joonsu's marker on Friday,
I can push out my own Hunter marker again.
[dealer] You can move it
from Friday to Saturday.
-[Sanghyun] I'll do that.
-[dealer] All right.
-Would you like to confirm this?
-Yes.
[dealer] All right, then.
Mr. Youn Sanghyun,
your Hunter marker has moved to Saturday.
-[Sanghyun] Thank you.
-Of course.
CAN ONLY MOVE YOUR OWN MARKER
TUE, WED
SANGHYUN
FRI: SANGHYUN
TUE: JUNSEO
TAKING ADVANTAGE
OF DAILY THREE-PLAYER LIMIT
THU, SAT
SANGHYUN
SANGHYUN PULLED OFF
HIS DESIRED MARKER PLACEMENTS
[♪ rock music playing]
RESULTS
[Sanghyun panting]
[Sanghyun] At that moment,
Junseo was waiting out front.
I thought, "This is actually good."
Because I moved
my Hunter marker to Saturday.
YUK JUNSEO, YOUN SANGHYUN
-[grunts]
-[host] Tag confirmed.
YOUN SANGHYUN, YUK JUNSEO
HORSEKING, SANGHYUN TIED
1ST SANGHYUN
2ND HORSEKING
[dealer] Mr. Youn Sanghyun,
congratulations.
Here is your 20 million won
and Elimination Immunity Pass.
-Your funds will be kept in your locker.
-Okay.
-[dealer] Please return to the Main Hall.
-Thank you.
[Jimin groans]
[players laughing]
I guess he must have received
more of the Wolf's perks.
Oh...
But in the end...
I have no idea.
I need them to explain what happened.
He said he knew the rules.
-Sanghyun knew.
-[Jimin] You knew the rules? Tell me.
So...
Well...
I looked around the Dealer Room carefully.
-Why am I stuttering?
-No, go ahead.
[Sanghyun] The dealer
-was wearing contact lenses.
-[exclaims]
[Sanghyun] That seemed a little strange.
So I checked his back,
and he had the same spot
for patches as we did.
[gasps]
A Wolf!
So I thought, "He's a Wolf."
Then...
There was one extra Wolf all along,
-because the dealer...
-He was that one Wolf.
[gasps, chuckles]
-[Jimin gasps] You're a genius.
-[gasps]
[Jieun] That's unbelievable.
I had no idea! How would I know? [groans]
I even heard them talk about it
before going into the room,
but I thought, "What different eyes?"
How did he figure that out?
I still don't get it.
I just thought the theme
of the dealer's outfit was a Wolf.
Geez.
I thought he was just in costume as a Wolf
for the game's theme.
I didn't think beyond that.
I thought, "Okay, I see."
And I left it at that.
Then, I stuck a patch on him.
And I could see the marker placements
of all the players.
And I was allowed to change things.
So that's why mine was changed.
I could move my Wolf and Hunter markers.
You're such a keen...
[Sanghyun] I asked him
if I could take a look.
[Jimin] Even I have to think
that was a great move.
I have to admit that was a brilliant move.
Sanghyun is capable of pulling off
a great move like that.
I thought it'd be great if I could team up
with someone like him
in a future Main Match.
That's what I was thinking.
ALWAYS THINKING ALLIANCES
When we all went in to check,
I thought he was a Wolf.
Ah, first off, I was amazed
by how he figured that out.
I was really impressed
by his eye for detail.
It was freaking awesome.
It was so amazing.
[gasps in awe]
That was an incredible idea.
It seems the perks were incredible.
That's the benefit of being the Seeker.
-[Horseking] Sorry?
-Is that the benefit of being the Seeker?
It doesn't make sense.
That could've been the Seeker's perk.
So I'm saying
they could make it look that way.
-[Jaegyun] Right.
-It could've been their only move to make.
In that case...
if we look at it from various angles,
that itself could be the advantage.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
Here's what I think.
The Seeker always has absolute power
and they can decide whether they want
to finish first or second.
If you look at it that way,
"MARKER MOVEMENT PASS
IS SEEKER'S PERK?"
what you're saying
might be the Seeker's perk.
Here's what I think.
A lot of you already suspected me.
I was honestly drawing a lot of suspicion.
In that situation, I wouldn't have to come
in first place if I were the Seeker.
Think about it.
Why would I try so hard
to take first place?
That's true.
[♪ intriguing music swells]
The players must have thought
that I was definitely the Seeker
and it was the Seeker's perk.
I guess that's what they suspected.
[mic feedback]
[host] We will reveal
the elimination candidate
from today's Main Match.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
The elimination candidate
from today's Main Match is...
ZZONE.
[ZZONE] I was bracing myself for it.
I was in serious trouble
and started to think
about who to pick as another candidate.
[host] We will announce
another elimination candidate.
[ZZONE] What? Who is it?
ANOTHER ELIMINATION CANDIDATE?
I wish I could turn back time.
[ZZONE] That means I have a second chance.
I was surely up for elimination,
but there might be a sliver of hope.
[host] The other
elimination candidate is...
Shin Jieun.
[sighs softly]
[players gasp]
[ZZONE] It was shocking.
But I was so relieved.
I was on the verge of being eliminated,
I saw this as a great opportunity.
[gasps]
I just had to hold out quietly
for 30 seconds.
But during those 30 seconds,
I was shaking from fear.
I kept hiding.
After hiding for so long,
I had a wake-up call.
I realized I was hiding like a coward
and waiting for someone else
to get eliminated.
I realized that wasn't my style.
So, I decided
to at least try to earn a point.
And I did some thinking.
It was Saturday, and Sanghyun was a Dog.
I was 99% sure.
I figured there was no way
I'd end up being pushed
into the bottom of the rankings.
So when I saw Sanghyun,
I rushed over and tagged him.
[Sanghyun] Why are you chasing me?
SANGHYUN & JIEUN TAG EACH OTHER
Let's go.
I got points out of this, so I was glad.
So I tagged her at the same time.
Also, her score went below -20
while I got points.
SHIN JIEUN
[laughing]
[groans]
[host] ZZONE and Shin Jieun
are elimination candidates.
[sighs] At the end, I shouldn't have...
[♪ tense music playing]
[Joonsu] The three of us were a team.
And the two of them
became elimination candidates.
Ah, it was such a shame.
But I didn't get picked.
[host] Since there are
two elimination candidates,
today's elimination candidate
will be decided by the winner,
Youn Sanghyun.
[sighs]
-That's going to be hard.
-[host] Youn Sanghyun.
-He'll be making an enemy.
-[host] Please go to the Dealer Room
and choose one player
between ZZONE and Shin Jieun.
First place comes with insane power.
You're not even going to give me
the chance to beg?
I polished my knees to beg.
[laughing]
[Jieun] I was so sad.
At the end, I shouldn't have messed
with Sanghyun, of all people.
[ZZONE] Sanghyun was looking at me.
I felt like he'd pick me
if I looked cheerful.
I was pretending to be helpless
so he'd feel sorry for me.
What should I do...
[Eunsil] Are you going right away?
[dealer] Mr. Youn Sanghyun,
please choose the elimination candidate.
SHIN JIEUN, ZZONE
[host] The elimination candidate
has been selected.
Between ZZONE and Shin Jieun,
the elimination candidate selected
by winner Youn Sanghyun is...
Shin Jieun.
IN TIME BETWEEN DOGS AND WOLVES,
SHIN JIEUN HAS BEEN ELIMINATED
[Sanghyun] I chose Shin Jieun
for elimination
because she suspected me
of being the Seeker.
I think Sanghyun is my number one suspect
-as the Seeker.
-Yeah.
Then, vote me out.
-I'm testing you.
-How many times will you say it?
Don't cry. Don't cry, don't cry.
And Horseking tagged Jieun.
-Here.
-No, wait.
I heard from Horseking
that they'd made a certain deal.
-You really need to help me.
-Me too.
I'll help you out later.
Seriously!
Anyhow, it was a battle
between me and Horseking.
Since she helped him,
I felt like she'd turned against me.
[Jieun] I knew he'd pick me.
I made him upset.
[ZZONE groans]
I survived. It was such a relief.
[host] Shin Jieun has been selected
by Youn Sanghyun
as the elimination candidate
and will now compete in the Death Match.
Please go to the Dealer Room
and pick two players besides Youn Sanghyun
who will join you in the Death Match.
[exhales heavily]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
-Ms. Shin Jieun.
-Yes?
Please select two elimination candidates.
[exhales heavily]
I feel like she'll pick male players.
There are two options.
She'll either pick weaker ones
for the Death Match
-or strong ones. It could be either way.
-Right.
I think she'll choose me and Junseo.
-I think it'll be me.
-[Joonsu] Why?
Just a hunch.
[Joonsu] ZZONE, Jieun, and I promised
we'd pick someone else
even if we ended up coming in last.
And no voting each other out.
-[ZZONE] Sounds good.
-Promise.
[Jieun] If I end up being eliminated,
I won't pick you.
[Joonsu] I didn't think it'd be me,
so I felt relieved.
It's taking quite a while.
[groans]
[sighs]
These two.
HORSEKING, YUK JUNSEO
[mic feedback]
[host] We will announce the results.
The players Shin Jieun chose
as her Death Match opponents are...
ZZONE
and Lee Joonsu.
[exclaims]
But they teamed up for the game.
-She picked them...
-That's unexpected.
...to win the match.
[Joonsu sighs] Jieun...
My heart just fell.
It felt worse than getting rejected
from college.
Why would she betray me?
[ZZONE] At that moment,
I was really annoyed.
[sighs frustratedly]
So she just picked
the easiest opponents to beat right away
in the Death Match.
Am I being dumb?
[groans] What a damn knucklehead.
ZZONE...
I actually want to pick these two,
but should I be selfish instead?
But they were on my team.
There were many moments
when I needed allies,
so I thought I might need allies
in the Death Match too.
So I thought it might be advantageous
to go with stronger players.
That's why I was going to pick these two.
HORSEKING, YUK JUNSEO
But this is a gamble, after all.
I kind of wanted to survive.
[groans]
I feel so guilty.
I found myself wanting to be
a bit more safe and make sure I survive.
I could team up with them,
or if I went head-to-head with them,
they were people I could beat.
I thought I should choose people
who'd fit both of those criteria.
[dealer] Your final choice
has been confirmed.
[sighs] Okay.
DEATH MATCH CANDIDATES
ZZONE AND LEE JOONSU
[Horseking] ZZONE and Joonsu
must be really stressed out.
[host] We'll now begin the vote
between the two candidates,
ZZONE and Lee Joonsu.
VOTING BEGINS
Voting will close in an hour.
-[Eunsil] Didn't you team up in the game?
-[ZZONE] We did. [chuckles]
-[Eunsil] She betrayed you.
-[ZZONE laughs]
-It's about survival.
-[Eunsil] That's true.
[ZZONE] I guess the two of us
were too focused on our alliance.
[Joonsu] But why us?
I don't get it.
[ZZONE] Because we're the easiest ones
to beat.
But we were a team.
This is ridiculous.
I genuinely trusted her.
-Help me.
-Go ahead.
[Joonsu] I let her tag me.
I even let her tag me on purpose
so she could get points.
Right.
[Joonsu] I even let her tag me.
[chuckles softly]
She was once our teammate,
so I don't want to ask her
for a favor with money.
I'll let them handle it.
I'll let them take care of it.
[Joonsu] Had it been someone else
and not ZZONE,
I would've offered 10 million won
and begged them not to pick me.
But ZZONE was on my team.
So I just figured
they'd pick the right person.
[dealer] Mr. Lee Joonsu,
please cast your vote for elimination.
[Joonsu] So I just voted for ZZONE
"JOONSU VOTED FOR ZZONE"
and decided to accept the results.
[exhales]
-[Joonsu] Are you crying? Why?
-Geez.
[chuckles, sniffles]
If I... [chuckles]
If I did well in the game,
-I would've spoken up.
-[Joonsu] You did well. We were a team.
Not really.
I was terrible.
[ZZONE] First, I was so upset
that I got betrayed.
On top of that, it was frustrating to lose
and become an elimination candidate.
All those emotions piled up
and came out as tears.
JOONSU IS AWAY FROM THE GROUP
AND KEEPS TO HIMSELF
[Horseking] Joonsu
is normally super social.
You have to help me this time.
Please help me.
JOONSU ACTIVELY WENT AROUND DURING VOTING
Please help me out just this once.
JOONSU IS UNUSUALLY QUIET THIS TIME
I really have no clue. What do I do?
The Seeker exists in this game.
I'm not sure if we should pick the person
we suspect is the Seeker.
[Jaegyun] What should we do?
Who should I pick?
If this is the case, let's have everyone
follow their instincts.
ELIMINATION CANDIDATE VOTE
LEE JOONSU
Joonsu would tell me
one thing,
but then act differently.
[Jaegyun] Hey, Joonsu tagged me twice.
IN ROUND 1
JOONSU ACTED LIKE HE TAGGED HIM
AND RAN AWAY
Where did he go?
So, we know one person will be ZZONE.
PROMISED TO VOTE OUT ZZONE WITH DAIL
ELIMINATION CANDIDATE VOTE
YANG DAIL
JOONSU VOTED FOR YANG DAIL
[Jaegyun] I thought he could become
a potential threat to me.
ELIMINATION CANDIDATE VOTE
[Horseking] I voted for ZZONE.
Joonsu is someone
who can cover my weak points.
He's able to move around
between different sides.
He keeps me updated on what he hears.
I think he's a really good partner.
[sighs]
[Jimin] I was really torn,
because I really like both.
It's partly because
they're such good listeners.
BEFORE SEEKER VOTE YESTERDAY
Horseking was able
to talk his way through it at the end,
and Pani Bottle fell for it.
I realized yesterday he was so persuasive.
ZZONE SUPPORTED JIMIN'S OPINION
-I wouldn't notice if he lied.
-I want to ask Joonsu this.
Do you still trust him?
I believed him up until now.
You don't suspect him as the Seeker?
I didn't, but I kind of do now.
-[Jimin] Come on!
-[players laugh]
GULLIBLE JOONSU
I have a lot to gain from these two,
so I don't want to lose them.
I'd rather take out someone
like Horseking, to be honest.
Wouldn't it be better to choose someone
who can come back then?
ELIMINATION CANDIDATE VOTE
JIMIN VOTED FOR JOONSU
I thought he'd do better and win,
so that's why I picked him.
[dealer] Ms. Jang Eunsil.
ELIMINATION CANDIDATE VOTE
JANG EUNSIL VOTED FOR JOONSU
[Eunsil] I was hoping
Joonsu would come back
after winning the Death Match
since he's the stronger player.
LEE JOONSU, 3 VOTES
JAEGYUN, EUNSIL, JIMIN
ZZONE, 2 VOTES
JOONSU, HORSEKING
-[dealer] Ms. ZZONE.
-Yes.
[dealer] Please vote
for the player to be eliminated.
ELIMINATION CANDIDATE VOTE
ZZONE
I didn't like how the prison players
had been seeing me
as an easy target since yesterday.
It's so annoying
that they thought I was the weakest one.
I wanted to return with my head held high
and prove myself.
I'll vote for myself.
LEE JOONSU, 3 VOTES
JAEGYUN, EUNSIL, JIMIN
ZZONE, 3 VOTES
JOONSU, HORSEKING, ZZONE
[host] We will announce the results.
The player who will be sent directly
to the Death Match is...
Lee Joonsu.
[ZZONE] What?
[Joonsu] I just felt upset.
[♪ rock music playing]
I don't know who to pick.
I have no idea.
-We should vote for Joonsu.
-[Sanghyun] Are you suspicious of him?
[Junseo] In every game,
I can't tell
if he's just naturally curious
or if he's intentionally
trying to stir things up.
I can't figure it out yet,
but it definitely bothers me.
JOONSU'S PLAY RAISED SUSPICIONS
That's why.
I think that makes sense.
[host] Lee Joonsu,
please leave the area immediately
and get ready for the Death Match.
I'll come back in one piece.
See you later.
[Joonsu] I will pull this off
and come back.
I'll win, no matter what.
People see me as the underdog,
and people are more likely
to feel sorry for me.
I'm starting to think,
"Maybe this isn't a bad thing."
[bell dings]
[Pani Bottle]
The Death Match is beginning.
We might end up going home today.
So let's look good until the end.
[laughs]
I got myself into the Death Match
like a God damn idiot.
Making stupid mistakes again
and getting eliminated is...
[exhales] ...something
I don't even want to imagine.
I don't care who gets taken out.
I need to survive.
[Sujin] I was put in prison from day one.
After staying in prison for a while,
I've had enough.
I need to survive this.
[Dail] We have to survive somehow.
At the end of the day,
it's all about the results.
I need to find out who the Seeker is.
We were committed to coming back
and catching the Seeker.
To the two people
coming to the Death Match,
I'm sorry,
but you'll need to go home first.
That's what I think.
MUYEONG MARKET
[Pani Bottle sighs]
[Ddolddol gasps]
It's like a haunted house.
[Sujin] I feel
an intense rush of dopamine.
I'm going to survive.
[Dail] Are we using
this entire outdoor area?
[Sujin] It's bigger than I thought.
[Dail] It's going to be exhausting.
Someone's waiting over there.
-It's Yuk Junseo.
-Who's that?
Hello.
Who is it?
It's not Yuk Junseo.
[Dail] I didn't know Joonsu
would be there.
But as for me,
I'm not intimidated by anyone.
I'm 99% sure I'll win.
[Ddolddol] Of all people,
it was Jieun, who's a girl,
and Joonsu, the youngest member,
so I felt a little bad.
Why? Because I know they're done for.
[chuckles]
[mic feedback]
[host] The loser of this Death Match
will become the first person eliminated,
and they will leave Deadly Tag.
[Joonsu] I'm going to return,
no matter what.
I need to take everyone down now.
[Jieun] I'll defeat everyone.
[host] The first Death Match
of Deadly Tag is...
"Time Case."
-"Time Case"?
[host] "Time Case"
is a six-player survival game,
in which time bombs
are hidden inside briefcases
and players must avoid
the case that explodes first.
The game will consist of two rounds.
The game area consists of six zones.
ZONE 1
ZONE 2
ZONE 3
ZONE 4
ZONE 5
ZONE 6
Once Round 1 begins,
starting from the player
most recently eliminated,
players will choose their cases.
The number on the case they choose
will become their zone.
The time inside the cases
will not be revealed.
But in Round 1,
there are two cases
with the shortest times,
and that time is 45 minutes.
The moment a case hits zero
and explodes...
-[explodes loudly]
-...the player holding that case
or the player whose zone the case is in
will be eliminated immediately.
PASS THE CASE
TO SOMEONE ELSE TO SURVIVE
Players can only move cases
that have entered their own zones.
Once a case is moved
to another player's zone,
the remaining time will be displayed
on the case for five seconds.
Each zone can have up to two cases
moved into it.
However, if a player holds two cases
for more than three minutes,
their case-holding capacity
will increase by one slot,
allowing them to hold up to three cases.
In Round 2,
all cases will be set to the same minute,
but the seconds will be set differently.
This is hard.
[host] In Round 2,
new cases will randomly appear
on the map during the game.
These cases give players an advantage
when attacking other players.
One player will be eliminated in Round 1,
and another will be eliminated in Round 2.
[sighs] I want to pray,
but who am I supposed to pray to?
[Ddolddol] I think the most crucial thing
was zone selection.
If you're in a zone
with too many nearby zones,
they're likely to bring the cases to me.
They didn't know
we played the Dogs and Wolves game
in this area.
I could see the entire map
and all the timers in a single glance.
[Dail] Physical strength
isn't that crucial in this game.
Once you decide on your target,
knowing how long it takes to get to them,
knowing how much time they have before
they can move the case somewhere else,
and remembering that
are much more important.
After going through different scenarios
in my head,
it turned out to be pretty easy.
[host] We will now begin
with case selection.
Starting with Lee Joonsu,
please enter the room one by one.
JOONSU GOES FIRST
AS MOST RECENT ELIMINATION
DEALER ROOM
Mr. Lee Joonsu, please select a case.
Ah...
Let's see. No. 2, No. 1.
No. 1, No. 2, No. 1, No. 2, No. 4.
JOONSU'S CHOICE
[dealer] Please proceed to Zone 4.
-[Jieun] Which one did you pick? No. 4?
-No. 4.
Ms. Shin Jieun, please select a case.
No. 4?
[sighs] No. 1...
[inhales sharply]
[dealer] Ms. Shin Jieun
has selected Case No. 1.
[Jieun] I placed myself
somewhere close to Joonsu on purpose,
because we'd already agreed
that we'd work together.
If teamwork is going to matter
in this game,
I thought you would be the better choice.
That's partly why I chose you.
JIEUN PROPOSES AN ALLIANCE
-[Joonsu] I'll crush everyone.
-I won't be scared.
[Jieun] Don't make it obvious
we're allied.
We'll be outnumbered.
Let's pretend we're not on the same side.
Let's stab them in the back.
Okay.
[Jieun] Joonsu.
Meet me here when it starts.
Meet me here.
[Ddolddol] For Round 1,
I was going to head to a corner by myself.
Thankfully, they picked No. 1 and No. 4.
The most isolated one, Zone 6, was empty.
I immediately picked No. 6.
KIM DDOLDDOL, ZONE 6
[dealer] Mr. Yang Dail
has selected Case No. 5.
Mr. Pani Bottle, please proceed to Zone 3.
Ms. Gyeong Sujin,
please proceed to Zone 2.
CASES AND ZONES HAVE BEEN SELECTED
[host] We will now begin
Round 0 of "Time Case."
Round 0 is the item-collection round.
You'll have five minutes to pick up items.
The items are in the form of cards
labeled with numbers.
You can apply an item card
to a case with the same number
-to adjust its timer...
-[timer ticking]
...and decrease it up to three minutes
or add to it up to three minutes.
We will now begin
Round 0.
[♪ exciting music playing]
[Pani Bottle] Okay.
No. 6.
Items...
I thought it was important.
It's the only variable that allows us
to change the time
we were initially given.
[Sujin] Nothing.
I was able to collect two items.
MEANWHILE, DAIL IS FULL OF CONFIDENCE
-I got the path figured out.
-[Pani Bottle] How?
[Dail] Come straight out that steel door,
and I'm right there.
[Pani Bottle]
There are six cases at first.
If there are two cases with longer times,
-we could pass them among us.
-[Dail] Right.
[Pani Bottle] Let's trade.
Let's share the times first. Okay.
[Dail] Someone's going to share with me
how much time is left
on a certain case?
I felt so reassured.
PANI BOTTLE AND DAIL TEAM UP
We don't have any sharp advantages,
but together we make a really good team.
Like puzzle pieces.
[Dail] The important part for me
was analyzing the routes.
Like, figuring out which paths
between zones were faster.
Managing just three nearby zones
was already overwhelming
and stressful in the game.
No. 5.
DAIL CAREFULLY STUDIES THE MAP LAYOUT
Go straight, and it's Zone 2.
It's so damn far.
[alarm blaring]
[host] We will now start Round 1
of "Time Case."
You may now move the Time Cases.
CASE TIMERS ON
[Joonsu] Hold on.
-Let's trade cases.
-[Jieun] Okay.
TIMER SHOWS FOR 5 SECONDS
IN ANOTHER PLAYER'S ZONE
ZONE 4
JOONSU'S ZONE
[Joonsu] How many minutes?
-Okay.
-[Jieun] It's 43 minutes.
[sighs]
Okay.
ZONE 3
PANI BOTTLE'S ZONE
Good.
ZONE 5
DAIL'S ZONE
It's 50 minutes. What's mine?
-It's 44 minutes.
-44 minutes?
ZONE 2
SUJIN'S ZONE
[Pani Bottle] Ddolddol!
Kim Ddolddol!
Yes, I'm right here.
-[Pani Bottle] Hold on.
-What?
[Pani Bottle] The best way
is to check the time and share it.
[Ddolddol] Right.
-[Pani Bottle] Tell me the time.
-What's the time now?
THE TWO SHARE TIMER INFORMATION
I believed Ddolddol would be
a reliable teammate I could count on.
So I asked him for help.
No. 4 has a lot of time left.
-There's 47 minutes.
-[Pani Bottle] Okay.
-[Ddolddol] This is 50 minutes.
-[Pani Bottle] No. 6? That's long. What?
Is it No. 5? No. 5 is the shortest.
No. 5 is the shortest? Okay.
THE CASES WITH THE SHORTEST TIMES
CASE 1
45 MINUTES
CASE 5
The first priority was figuring out
which cases had the shortest times left.
If I got the time bomb case
in either No. 1 or No. 5,
the key is where I place it
when it has only one minute left.
That's how I could eliminate someone.
I had a rough idea of the timers.
I walked around the game area.
Look.
Look at the map.
These areas are at a disadvantage.
Areas right in the middle,
like Zones 2 and 3.
ZONES 2 AND 3 ARE EASY TARGETS
ZONE 2, ZONE 3
THE MIDDLE ZONES ARE NEXT TO EACH OTHER
I thought, "This is not good."
ANXIOUS
I didn't want to be eliminated.
I was so desperate to stay in the game.
What we picked put us at a disadvantage.
We need to get rid of Gyeong Sujin.
GYEONG SUJIN APPEARS
In fact, while Sujin was in jail,
she suspected we might be the Seeker.
PANI BOTTLE WAS WORRIED
ABOUT SUJIN'S SUSPICIONS
We figured it wouldn't do any good
to keep her around.
[Dail] I agree with that too.
We'll have no choice
but to have her eliminated.
I realized that.
SUJIN SUDDENLY BECOMES A TARGET
Ddolddol!
[whispers] Come over here.
The Seeker is a player from prison.
-Really?
-Yes.
The reason why
I'm only telling you this
is because you're not a Seeker.
Just so you know.
[Ddolddol breathes deeply]
[Sujin] I thought I needed
to get inside people's heads.
APPROACHING JIEUN THIS TIME
Excuse me.
You know I'm not a Seeker, right?
-[Jieun] Yes.
-I really am not.
We have to catch the Seeker.
The ultimate goal of this game
is to catch the Seeker.
I was taken off
the list of possible Seekers
from the very beginning.
That's why they shouldn't eliminate me.
No one would doubt that.
IS IT A BLUFF OR THE TRUTH?
No one would suspect
that the person in prison was the Seeker.
[host] There are two Time Cases in Zone 2.
[Sujin] Here we go. This is serious.
THE ATTACKS BEGIN
If you leave two cases
for more than three minutes,
the number of slots goes up by one,
which makes things worse.
For that, I kept dropping cases
into her zone.
It was to check things out, to attack,
and to increase Sujin's slots.
It is what it is. This is about survival.
ONCE A CASE IS PLACED,
ONLY THE ZONE'S OWNER CAN MOVE IT
Trade, trade.
We'll exchange anyway.
First off, just attack.
[Sujin] This is exhausting. [pants]
TO SURVIVE, PASS THE CASE ON
[host] There are two Time Cases in Zone 2.
[exhales]
[Sujin sighs]
There are two Time Cases in Zone 2.
I heard "Zone 2" so many times
that it got stuck in my head.
JOONSU WATCHES IT ALL UNFOLD
[Joonsu] There were barrels
in front of her zone,
so I set them down
to make it harder for them to move around.
[host] There are two Time Cases in Zone 2.
Come on, don't do this. What's with them?
[exhales frustratedly]
I got really mad.
JOONSU BLOCKS THE PATH WITH THE BARREL
[Joonsu] I had to do
what needed to be done.
I have to survive.
[thuds]
[Sujin] Excuse me.
What do you think you're doing?
[Dail] I didn't do that.
[Sujin] Is this how they're trying to win?
I understand. It's a game, after all.
Fine, let's see
who wins in the end.
SUJIN APPROACHES JIEUN
-We need to put...
-[Jieun] Yes?
[Sujin] ...two cases in Dail's zone.
I've got a plan.
SUJIN'S TARGET IS DAIL
[Jieun] Keep putting them there?
Got it. I'll place it there.
SUJIN WALKS PAST DAIL
[Dail] Every time we crossed paths,
I worried, "What if she puts the bomb
on me at the end?"
It felt so unfair.
The more time passed,
the more it felt like it'd come down
to a last-second battle.
NO. 1 AND NO. 5 WILL EXPLODE IN 12 MINUTES
Do you know where No. 1 and 5 are?
-No. 1 and 5 have the shortest time left.
-[Dail] No. 1, 5?
We need to know where they are.
No. 1, No. 5. No. 1, No. 5.
CASE NO. 1 AND NO. 5 GO MISSING
[host] There are two Time Cases in Zone 6.
[Pani Bottle] I think
they're at Zone 6. Hold on.
[groans] Fuck!
Ddolddol!
Ddolddol.
Where did he go?
Ddolddol!
Hang on, what's going on? Something's off.
Where is he?
[Dail] Pani Bottle.
[Pani Bottle] Dail.
Have you seen Ddolddol?
-[Dail] I haven't.
-Where is he?
PANI BOTTLE AND DAIL ARE CONFUSED
Do you know where No. 1 and No. 5 are?
[Pani Bottle] I think they're at Zone 6.
We need to find out
who's holding No. 1 and 5.
[Pani Bottle sighs frustratedly]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
SOMEONE'S HIDING THE CASES ON PURPOSE?
[panting]
[Sujin] They were all in my zone.
JOONSU WAS PASSING BY SUJIN'S ZONE
[Pani Bottle] Joonsu.
Both No. 1 and No. 5
are in Zone 2 right now.
-In Sujin's zone.
-[Pani Bottle] No.
[breathing heavily]
They can't come to me at the end.
[Dail] I realized
I really needed to stay alert.
IT'S FINALLY TIME TO MAKE A MOVE
PANI BOTTLE VISITS DAIL
-Are you sure? That this...
-No. 5 has 20 minutes on it.
-If it's shorter...
-Then leave No. 4 to me.
-Leave it to me now.
-Right now?
DAIL TAKES OFF AT PANI BOTTLE'S REQUEST
SUJIN'S TARGET IS DAIL
[host] There are two Time Cases in Zone 5.
[Ddolddol] Be careful.
RUNNING IN PANIC
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[timer ticking]
[exhales]
[panting]
[timer ticking]
THE TIME ON CASE NO. 1 SUDDENLY DROPS
[Dail] What the heck? I'm fucked.
ONLY TWO MINUTES UNTIL EXPLOSION
What kind of bastard...
I'm so fucked.
EARLIER
DEALER ROOM
[Sujin] I went to the Dealer Room
and shortened the time.
Minus three minutes on Case No. 1.
[panting]
Geez, all the cases
with the shortest times are coming to me.
I thought I might actually lose.
[breathing heavily]
Sujin kept leaving the cases in my zone.
If I played smart, I still had a chance
to turn things around.
To buy as much time as possible
before she could reach me,
I had to go a little far.
So I dragged things out with Case No. 1.
I stalled with Case No. 1.
-[panting]
-[timer ticking]
[timer beeping]
ONE MINUTE BEFORE EXPLOSION
[breathes heavily]
They should come this way.
[footsteps]
JIEUN'S ZONE AND NOT SUJIN'S
For me, the farthest place
was Jieun's zone,
so I passed through Joonsu
and dropped it over at Jieun's.
[timer beeping rapidly]
[case explodes]
[Sujin panting]
[sighs]
[host] Gyeong Sujin's Time Case
has exploded.
1 MINUTE AGO
[Jieun] I could actually see Dail hiding.
But it felt like
he was trying to stall for time.
So I pretended to leave the area.
The case had 44 seconds left.
I didn't have time to think.
I thought I had to take out
whoever was closest to me.
That happened to be Sujin.
NOT ENOUGH TIME TO GET BACK AT DAIL
[panting]
Where's the case? Case No. 1.
No way.
I went back thinking, "No way."
Which case is it?
No. 1.
[Sujin] Not No. 1.
I'm screwed.
I was taken out by the card I used.
[clicks tongue]
[sighs] This is where it ends for me.
[mic feedback]
[host] Round 1 is over.
[Dail groans]
that was brutal as hell. [sighs]
[sighs, groans]
[sighs]
[gasps]
[host] Before we begin Round 2
of "Time Case,"
due to her Time Case exploding,
Gyeong Sujin
-has been eliminated.
-[exclaims]
[♪ somber music playing]
Good work, everyone.
-Good job, everyone.
-[Sujin] That was a great game.
[sighs]
Hope you make it to the end.
Sujin, it's really a misunderstanding.
I swear, I didn't block it.
It really wasn't me. Trust me.
FIRST ELIMINATION IS GYEONG SUJIN
-[Joonsu] Good work.
-Let's have a drink later.
[Sujin chuckles]
[Jieun] I felt so bad for her.
[Ddolddol] I was really sad
when I heard Sujin was out.
[Dail] Thank you, and sorry, Sujin.
But I had no choice.
I came here to survive,
so I had to put my survival first.
[host] We will now begin
with case selection for Round 2.
TIME CASE ROUND 2
In Round 2, the seconds for every case
will be set at different times.
We will now start
Time Case selection to change zones.
Excluding Gyeong Sujin,
we will start with the player holding
the case with the shortest remaining time.
Shin Jieun, please enter first.
[Jieun] This works in my favor.
I thought I had to make the most
of this opportunity.
[clears throat, sniffles]
How many cards do you have?
Do we have two cases coming in?
RIGHT AFTER JIEUN LEAVES
-One, right?
-Two will spawn.
Listen. Just keep your own case
and stay where you are.
-I know.
-[Ddolddol] When someone comes over,
we rotate it and check the time.
We need to keep sharing the timer
on the two cases that respawn.
-Then repeat.
-Let's pass the cases around among us.
[♪ tense music playing]
[sniffles]
[Joonsu] I really just stayed still
because I was scared.
If you were in my position,
you'd understand.
I had only one thought in my head.
Win, no matter what.
That's all I could think of.
Ms. Shin Jieun, please select a Time Case.
This one.
-Put anything that spawns there.
-Exactly.
TALKS QUICKLY END WHEN JIEUN RETURNS
That should be safer.
-I'm always worried.
-[Jieun] I'm cold.
[hisses]
[clears throat]
[Jieun] Zone 6 was more isolated
than the other areas.
I didn't want to rule out the possibility
that they could attack whoever was closest
if they fell into an emergency situation.
I thought it was absolutely worth a shot.
[host] Kim Ddolddol, please enter.
[dealer] Mr. Kim Ddolddol
has selected Case No. 4.
[Pani Bottle] I'll go with No. 5.
[dealer] Okay,
you have selected Case No. 5.
[host] Lee Joonsu, please enter.
I'm the last one. [sighs frustratedly]
What did Jieun choose? She chose...
Pani Bottle got No. 4.
Then...
I tried to choose a zone
that was as close as possible to Jieun.
I'll go with No. 3.
[dealer] Mr. Lee Joonsu,
you have selected Case No. 3.
Thank you.
Mr. Yang Dail, there's only one case left.
Okay.
Case No. 2.
DAIL TAKES CASE NO. 2
ROUND 2 CASES AND ZONES HAVE BEEN SELECTED
[alarm blaring]
[host] Round 2 of "Time Case"
will begin now.
[Pani Bottle]
Leave it here. Don't kill it.
ZONE 5
PANI BOTTLE'S ZONE
Don't kill it.
[host] There are two Time Cases in Zone 5.
ZONE 2
DAIL'S ZONE
In Round 2, the seconds for every case
will be set at different times.
SHORTEST TIMES
[♪ tense music playing]
[Jieun] I looked around for a moment.
Judging by the atmosphere,
something felt a little off.
[coughs] Why is nothing here?
No one left cases in my area,
and it was unexpected.
DDOLDDOL IS STANDING IN PLACE
[Dail] Thirty minutes.
[Pani Bottle] We can't put it yet.
Three minutes have to pass.
Once three minutes pass,
-a notice pops up.
-Right.
[Pani Bottle] When it does,
just place it and we're done.
I went into Round 2 thinking,
"Even if I wanted to lose, I couldn't."
It was basically in the bag.
How could I possibly lose?
I can't possibly lose.
[Pani Bottle] As for the penalty,
there are two cases.
Once it passes three minutes,
you can place up to three cases.
It might seem like a bad thing,
but if three cases with long timers
come in, you can't put any more.
I'm not really the type
who understands game rules instantly.
[host] Each zone can have
up to two cases moved into it.
However, if a player holds two cases
for more than three minutes,
"WHAT EVERYONE THOUGHT WAS A PENALTY"
their case-holding capacity
will increase by one slot,
allowing them to hold up to three cases.
CAN'T PLACE ANY MORE CASES
[Pani Bottle] That's when I realized
I should take advantage of this
and block out cases.
I tested it out in Round 1.
When Sujin saw the cases in my area,
"HIS ZONE WAS FULL WITH THREE"
I saw her go, "Geez" and walk away.
I thought, "Okay, we got it."
Whether it was Yuk Junseo
or Horseking who came,
I could eliminate anyone.
It's a sure-win strategy.
It doesn't matter who goes first.
Just go and join Sujin.
ZONE 2
DAIL'S ZONE
[Ddolddol] Which number is it?
No. 6.
Jieun left it at my zone.
[Ddolddol] Is it hers?
[Dail] It's quite far from here.
We can't put two in your zone.
We should put them somewhere closer.
Then, they'll get fucked on the way.
[Ddolddol] What's the number of mine?
What's your number?
-No. 2?
-Yes, No. 2.
BLOCKING ZONE CHANGES BASED ON DAIL'S IDEA
-[Ddolddol] Is yours empty?
-It's empty.
ZONE 2
DAIL'S ZONE
It's 27 minutes. It's similar.
-[host] There are two Time Cases...
-A bit longer.
-...in Zone 2.
-[Ddolddol] No. 4 is a bit shorter.
-I'll check.
-Okay.
ZONE 5
PANI BOTTLE'S ZONE
[host] Zone 5's slots
have increased to three.
-So three slots in Zone 5?
-[Joonsu] Here.
Then we'd better move one
from here to there.
[Dail] But that's far.
It's better to move it somewhere closer.
-That zone already has three slots.
-[Dail] We can make it three here too.
There shouldn't be three here.
Otherwise, the cases might end up here.
There has to be only one zone
with three slots.
[Dail] So, put two here.
[Ddolddol] No,
there shouldn't be three here.
The cases might end up here.
We should block that in the first place.
[Dail] I couldn't understand it.
Because either way,
Pani's zone is far from Jieun's.
Jieun would go to somewhere closer
for an attack.
Then shouldn't we block this spot
to make Jieun go back and forth farther?
What's the point of blocking it here?
-[Pani Bottle] What's with No. 5?
-Move it fast.
-Let's move No. 5. Hurry.
-Move No. 5.
[Pani Bottle] Are there two No. 5s?
-[exclaims]
-[Pani Bottle] Why?
[Dail] I didn't say it,
but I thought to myself,
"I can't believe him."
Even while helping us,
he's making a backup plan.
I can't believe Pani Bottle.
He's looking for a way
to survive alone now?
I still enjoyed it.
Even if I messed up,
I wouldn't get eliminated.
[Ddolddol] Put it here,
and don't touch it at all.
[Pani Bottle] We need to spread out now.
[Ddolddol] Don't touch No. 5
and spread out.
-[host] Zone 2 now has three slots.
-Split up...
-[Ddolddol sighs]
-[Pani Bottle] Zone 2?
NO. 4 CASE TIMER
[Pani Bottle] Why?
INCLUDING TRAVEL TIME,
EXCEEDED THREE MINUTES
-So we could put several there as well?
-[Pani Bottle groans]
Why would it increase to three?
[Ddolddol] I don't know.
It must've passed three minutes.
[Pani Bottle sighs] Shit.
I didn't see this coming.
I don't think I'll be eliminated.
I'm afraid someone on my side
might end up getting eliminated.
Let's go all out, no matter what.
ZONE 6 IS STILL EMPTY
ZONE 6 SHIN JIEUN
CASES ARE CLUSTERED IN ZONES 2, 3, 5
[Jieun] Zone 3...
-[Joonsu] What are you looking for?
-I'm not looking for anything.
I believe they're not letting me
know the time left on purpose
by not placing any cases.
I was supposed to know the timers
so I could make predictions.
But with no cases in my zone,
I had no way of knowing.
[Joonsu] Yes, that makes sense.
Be careful.
[Jieun] Just let me know the time
once you find out.
Or you can move my case over later.
I couldn't communicate with him.
You know how many minutes are left?
-The case?
-I don't know.
Damn it...
[Joonsu] Where on earth are they?
JOONSU IS LOOKING FOR THE SPAWNED CASES
[object scrapes]
[groans] Where did they hide it?
Unbelievable.
[alarm blaring]
[host] A new case
has been added to the Maze.
A NEW CASE IN THE MAZE
Only the first two arriving players
can claim the cases.
[Pani Bottle] Fuck.
The second I heard the announcement,
I began running.
If Jieun happens to find them in the maze,
my plan's done for, so I ran like hell.
DAIL ARRIVES AT THE MAZE FIRST
[Dail] I ran like crazy because of this.
I found it.
I quickly got in and picked up the case.
[Ddolddol] Add this to my zone.
One more. Give it to me.
PRISON MATES GET SPAWNED CASES
[Pani Bottle] Look at the time.
ZONE 3
JOONSU'S ZONE
[Ddolddol] Look at this.
-[Pani Bottle] There's 13 minutes.
-Okay. No. 7 has 13 minutes.
JIEUN WAS MONITORING THE PRISON MEMBERS
[host] There are two Time Cases in Zone 3.
Zone 3?
DDOLDDOL AND PANI BOTTLE'S
SUSPICIOUS MOVES
-[Ddolddol] Hold on.
-[Pani Bottle] Let's go to Dail.
SPOTS SHIN JIEUN
I need to check the timer on No. 8.
PRISON MEMBERS BECOME FRANTIC
ZONE 4
DDOLDDOL'S ZONE
[Dail] I saw it had barely any time left.
I passed Case No. 8 to the other two.
-What I brought over is No. 8.
-No. 8.
Just focus on that.
We need to get this done now.
-[Ddolddol] What?
-If I cut three minutes, it becomes six.
So we have to do it now.
I'll bring it when it's almost a minute.
PANI BOTTLE CAN ATTACK NO. 8?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
JIEUN STAYS CALM
[Jieun] I thought they had
the upper hand in location
when it came to finding them,
so I kept thinking about
how I should deal with it.
I decided to focus on defense first.
SHIN JIEUN
SHE LEFT HER POSITION ON PURPOSE
IN ROUND 1
SHIN JIEUN
JIEUN STAYS AWAY FROM HER ZONE ON PURPOSE
[Pani Bottle] Now six minutes? Or five?
-We can't have it blow up in our hands.
-Right.
Go slow and I'll use it right away.
-Right now?
-[Ddolddol] No.
Set it off 15 seconds later.
Okay, 15, 14, 13...
DDOLDDOL MOVES CASE NO. 8
Twelve, eleven, ten,
"PANI BOTTLE GOES TO DEALER ROOM"
nine, eight, seven...
...three,
two,
one.
ZONE 6
JIEUN'S ZONE
[host] There are two Time Cases in Zone 6.
My plan was to act clueless the whole time
and strike at the last second.
So I took off running.
DEALER ROOM
[dealer] Would you like to use an item?
I'll take three minutes away
on Case No. 8.
[dealer] Case No. 8's timer
will be reduced by three minutes.
[host] An item was applied to Case No. 8.
[Joonsu] Jieun, no! Damn it.
[case explodes]
[host] Shin Jieun's Time Case
has exploded.
[Jieun] What happened?
I heard that my case... [chuckling]
...had suddenly exploded.
DEALER ROOM
1 MINUTE AGO
Would you like to use an item?
I'll take three minutes away
on Case No. 8.
PANI BOTTLE CAME BACK RIGHT AWAY
I'll take three minutes away
from Case No. 8.
USED THE NO. 8 CARD AGAIN
In the middle of the game,
Joonsu came over to me.
So...
BEFORE ROUND 2 BEGAN
Round 2 is going to be all about politics.
We need to take them out here.
-There's no reason to keep them around.
-[Joonsu] I agree.
Forget about alliances.
I was in a position
where I could be betrayed at any moment.
[host] The players Shin Jieun chose
as her Death Match opponents are...
Lee Joonsu.
-How many did you find?
-[Joonsu] Three.
-[Jieun] Give me one. Give me one.
-[Joonsu] I'll find one.
JOONSU WAS HESITANT
[Jieun] Did you hear me?
[Joonsu] I couldn't stop suspecting Jieun.
I was afraid I'd get betrayed again.
I figured, to survive,
I'd have to betray her first.
I had to prove
to the guys that I could be useful.
I found one.
Thank you.
-Hey, take this.
-Thank you.
Luckily, the two cards
Joonsu gave me in a hurry
happened to be two eights.
When I saw that,
I was completely relieved.
This time, I knew I was safe. Okay.
The game was pretty much over then.
I'll climb back up.
I'll survive and make it back.
That's all I could think of.
-Another No. 8?
-Yes, minus three minutes.
[dealer] All right. Case No. 8's timer
will be reduced by three minutes.
[host] An item was applied to Case No. 8.
-Shin Jieun's Time Case...
-[sighs]
...has exploded.
[Jieun] I think
I'd already come to terms with it.
[host] "Time Case" is over.
But getting eliminated first
is a little too much.
[chuckling] I'm kind of mad.
[host] We will announce the results
of the Death Match.
Everyone, please gather in the Main Hall.
The contestants eliminated from Deadly Tag
after today's Death Match
are Gyeong Sujin
and Shin Jieun.
Gyeong Sujin and Shin Jieun,
please exit the area immediately.
[sighs]
[♪ pensive music playing]
Eliminated players
will not be able to return to Deadly Tag.
I'll get going.
Good job, everyone.
[Sujin] I wish you the best of luck.
-Good work.
-[Sujin] Bye.
-Take care.
-[player] Keep in touch.
-[Jieun] I've grown so attached now.
-I know.
Because of the last 10 seconds...
[Pani Bottle sighs]
[Sujin sighs heavily]
-[Jieun] You did so great.
-[Sujin] It's such a shame.
-It's such a shame. [sighs]
-[Jieun] It really is.
I was really motivated and driven.
I feel like I went through
this prison life...
-There's no one.
-...more intensely than anyone else.
-[Ddolddol] Want me to clean this up?
-No, it's fine.
I think the game itself was a lot of fun.
This experience made me understand
how important politics are...
-[explodes]
-[yelps]
...in a survival game.
SUJIN GAVE IT HER BEST AT EVERY MOMENT
What's with them?
I think I'm actually a very soft person
deep down inside.
But as I played this game...
-Run!
-I wanted to show my cool and tough side.
I wanted to do whatever it took
to win by being selfish
or by betraying others.
I wanted to show that side of me.
But while playing the game, I found myself
just having fun
and getting along with everyone.
[chuckles]
Get him, get him!
[grunts]
I enjoyed spending time
with such wonderful people
on this program.
[♪ emotional music playing]
I had such a great time.
I'm sad that it's over,
but when you think about it,
there's only one winner
and I just got eliminated a little sooner.
They'll get eliminated one by one
in their own time.
I hope they do their best out there.
I'm leaving with some regrets,
but I'll get going.
FINAL ELIMINATIONS
GYEONG SUJIN, SHIN JIEUN
[Pani Bottle sighs]
So this is the Main Hall.
Let's do a toast.
-[Ddolddol] Good work.
-Cheers.
[exhales]
Mmm!
Are you going to bed, Horseking?
-I don't know.
-[Pani Bottle] Okay.
AWKWARD RESPONSE FROM OTHERS
-[Ddolddol] See you tomorrow.
-Good night.
[Ddolddol] I don't think
we're exactly welcome.
I don't think we're exactly welcome.
Even better.
This is exactly what I wanted.
They reacted like, "There are
more survivors than I expected."
Like, "Get a load of these punks."
I love it.
Let's crush them all.
[Pani Bottle and Ddolddol laughing]
[Ddolddol] Because they're all rivals.
[chuckles]
[Pani Bottle]
The three of us had this mindset
that we'd return and crush everyone.
[Dail] I don't think anyone could beat us.
I think the entire dynamic will change.
[distorted voice] Yeah,
tear each other apart and fight it out.
[laughing maniacally]
[Pani Bottle sighs frustratedly]
God damn it!
This is making me angry.
The prison team is too intimidating.
The prison crew is insane.
[Dail] I want to punch them.
It's fun.
It's not fun for me.
[Jimin] The prison team seemed
to be banding together so closely.
It's intimidating, but at the same time...
[Horseking] The prison team's getting
a little too full of themselves.
[host] This Main Match
is a team competition called "Kingmaker."
[Dail] The prison team's getting
a little too full of themselves.
[Pani Bottle]
Keep the strong players in check.
[Ddolddol] Yuk Junseo, Horseking?
Tag them, no matter what.
[Junseo] Catch them!
[Horseking]
Run like your life depends on it.
-[Ddolddol] Horseking is here!
-[Dail] Where did he go?
[Dail] The game is ours.
[Junseo] What? [groans]
[Horseking] I'm confused.
[Junseo] Fuck.
[Ddolddol] Oh my, look at this.
Horseking and Yuk Junseo
have been crippled.
[host] The contestants eliminated
from Deadly Tag are...
[♪ ominous music playing]
Translated by Youji Kim